FONG WEI ZHENG

Mobile: 93543053

E-mail: E0035221@u.nus.edu

Github: https://github.com/fongwz

PROFILE

I am a year 3 computer engineering student current studying at the National University of Singapore. As a prospective computer engineer, I have worked on both the hardware and software side of products and applications.

During my time at NUS, I have also participated in various external and internal hackathons, such as the SWSG hackathon in September 2017, and NUS's Games Development hackathon in December 2017.

Through internships, I want to further my skill sets and experience the feeling of a real working environment to prepare for life after graduation

EXPERIENCE

Linde Gas Asia Pte Ltd

Software Engineer Intern June 2018 - August 2020 Worked in the digital acceleration department, and helped them out with their projects to digitalize Linde's internal processes.

- -Created dashboards for various projects
- -Used the Raspberry Pi to create a facial recognition device
- -Worked with OpenCV to perform some simple image processing

Microsoft Operation Pte Ltd

Admin Assistant January 2014 - April 2014 Worked as as a temporary staff to assist the licensing team in performing simple data processing and data I/O

EDUCATION

National University of Singapore

Bachelor of Engineering(Computer Engineering) August 2016 - Current

SKILLS

- C#
- C++
- Python
- Java, JavaFX
- PHP, React.JS, Node.JS
- Verilog
- ARM Assembly